http://www.homecareappliances.co.uk/privacy-policy-i4

X
This site uses cookies to provide and improve your shopping experience.
If you want to benefit from this improved service, please opt-in.
For more information, please see our
Cookies Page.
My Wishlist
(0)
Fitted Kitchens and Appliances
• Kitchens - Classic Fitted• Kitchens - Modern Fitted• Kitchen Taps• Kitchen Sinks• Worktops• Range Cookers• Freestanding Cookers• Hobs• Hoods• Splashbacks• Dishwashers• Refrigeration
Bathroom Suites, Shower Rooms and Cloakrooms
• Bathroom Suites• Furniture• Bathroom Taps• Showers & Valves• Shower Enclosures• Baths• Basins• Toilets• Bidets• Bath Panels• Bathroom Accessories• Bath Screens• Trays• Shower Board• Towel Warmers
• Brison Exclusive Bathrooms
• Tiles
Fitted Bedroom Furniture
• Bedroom Classic fitted furniture• Bedroom Modern fitted furniture• Bedroom Sliding Wardrobe Doors• Home Office fitted furniture• Chest of drawers
Heating, Woodburners, Stoves, Fires & Fireplaces
• Stoves• Gas Fires• Electric Fires• Wooden Fire Surrounds• Limestone Fireplaces• Marble Fireplaces• Electric Suites• Fireplace Mirrors• Inglenook Chambers• Cast Iron Inserts• Hearths and Back Panels• Designer Radiators• Radiators
• Pipe & Fittings
• Heating Controls
• Fireside Accessories
• Flue Pipe & Systems
• Solid Fuel Spares
• Firewood & Coal
Brands
1909AqataBayswaterBC DesignsBellaBrison FireplacesBrison Fitted BedroomsBrison Fitted KitchensBushboardCast TecDimplexDimplex Display and DemonstrateDovreDunsleyDunsley SoloEcoElgin and Hall
EReflex Skope by GazcoEssential BathroomsEssential FireplacesEssential HeatingEvolution by BroseleyEvonicF2 FiresFalconFirefoxGazcoGlidor by BAHeritageHunterIlektro Paul Agnew DesignIndaInspire by ValorIntensity
KatellKindredKitchen StoriKudosLaura AshleyNEFFNu-FlameNuance by BushboardOn Trend KitchensOranierOrigins by UtopiaParkrayPenmanPronto by BAPryzm by Elgin & HallRadiance by GazcoRangemaster
Roper RhodesSecond NatureSmedboSmegStovaxTigerUltraHeatVadoValorValor CentreValoreVarde OvneVitraWaters Baths of AshbourneYeomanZurfiz by BAView All
About Us
Contact Us
Home › Privacy Policy
Customer Service
Privacy Policy
GDPR Privacy Notice
From 25th May 2018 the General Data Protection Regulations come into force.  This means we must inform you of the data we hold for you and how we use it.
Our lawful basis requesting and processing your personal information is to either provide you with a quotation or to fulfil our contractual obligation to you in the form of a sale of goods and / or services.
We are committed to protecting your privacy. All information will be collected lawfully and in accordance with the General Data Protection Regulations.
We collect information about you for 2 reasons:•    firstly, to process your order•    secondly, to provide you with the best possible service.
We will not e-mail you in the future unless you have given us your consent. We will not pass your e-mail address to other trusted traders unless you agree.The type of information we will collect about you includes:•    your name•    address•    phone number•    email address•    credit/debit card details
We will never collect sensitive information about you without your explicit consent.The information we hold will be accurate and up to date. You can check the information that we hold about you by emailing us. If you find any inaccuracies we will delete or correct it promptly.The personal information which we hold will be held securely in accordance with our internal security policy and the law.If we intend to transfer your information outside the EEA (European Economic Area) we will always obtain your consent first.
We may use technology to track the patterns of behaviour of visitors to our site. This can include using a "cookie" which would be stored on your browser. You can usually modify your browser to prevent this happening. The information collected in this way can be used to identify you unless you modify your browser settings.This does not affect your statutory rights as a consumer.Data Protection Registration No: Z6166804
Continue BrowsingVisit our Homepage.
');
-->
Tweet
eCommerce by Visualsoft
